<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Blue Board — United Airlines Flight Tracker</title>
    <link>https://theblueboard.co</link>
    <description>Real-time United Airlines operations dashboard. Live flight tracking, hub delay monitoring, Starlink WiFi fleet status, and operational analytics for all 9 United hubs.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://theblueboard.co/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines Live Flight Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co</guid>
      <description>Track every United Airlines flight in real time. 600+ flights on a live map updated every 30 seconds. Hub delay alerts, IRROPS monitoring, flight search, and weather radar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines Fleet Database — 1,078 Aircraft</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/fleet</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/fleet</guid>
      <description>Complete United Airlines fleet database. Search 1,078 mainline aircraft by type, registration, seat configuration, WiFi, and Starlink status. Boeing 737, 757, 767, 777, 787, Airbus A319, A320, A321neo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines Hub Airports — All 9 Hubs</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs</guid>
      <description>Live status at all 9 United Airlines hub airports. Delays, cancellations, on-time performance at ORD, DEN, IAH, EWR, SFO, IAD, LAX, NRT, and GUM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at Chicago O'Hare (ORD) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/ord</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/ord</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at Chicago O'Hare. Real-time delays, cancellations, on-time performance, Starlink WiFi, and schedules. United's largest hub with ~750 daily departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at Denver (DEN) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/den</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/den</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at Denver International. Delays, cancellations, on-time performance, Starlink WiFi. United's second-largest hub with ~540 daily departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at Houston (IAH) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/iah</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/iah</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at Houston Intercontinental. Delays, cancellations, on-time performance. United's Latin America gateway with ~400 daily departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at Newark (EWR) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/ewr</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/ewr</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at Newark Liberty. Delays, cancellations, on-time performance. United's East Coast transatlantic gateway with ~400 daily departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at San Francisco (SFO) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/sfo</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/sfo</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at San Francisco International. Delays, cancellations, on-time performance. United's Asia-Pacific gateway with ~300 daily departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at Washington Dulles (IAD) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/iad</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/iad</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at Washington Dulles. Delays, cancellations, on-time performance. ~250 daily departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at Los Angeles (LAX) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/lax</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/lax</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at Los Angeles International. Delays, cancellations, on-time performance. United's Pacific gateway with ~200 daily departures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at Tokyo Narita (NRT) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/nrt</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/nrt</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at Tokyo Narita International. United's Asian hub connecting Pacific routes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines at Guam (GUM) — Hub Status</title>
      <link>https://theblueboard.co/hubs/gum</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theblueboard.co/hubs/gum</guid>
      <description>Live United Airlines status at Guam International. United's Pacific island hub.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
